{
    "id": "0b2b950b46744fca81cb945ba33ee71c",
    "title": "Do, does and did worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "f7d7820686eb488ba182fe9c585546cb",
            "title": "Do, Does And Did Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "..................... you know where he is going?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Do",
                        "Does",
                        "Did"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………….. she understand the importance of working hard?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Do",
                        "Does",
                        "Did"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "..................... they hold all-night parties?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Do",
                        "Does",
                        "Did"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where ..................... they live?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does",
                        "did"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "How …………………. you operate this washing machine?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does",
                        "did"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "What ………………… you do then?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does",
                        "did"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………. not know that I was playing with fire.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "did",
                        "do",
                        "does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………. she say anything when you told her that you were leaving?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Do",
                        "Does",
                        "Did"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Samuel ………………… not work.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does",
                        "did"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Martha and Samuel …………………. not appreciate the dignity of labor.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "does",
                        "did"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Peter ………………….. not know the answer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "does",
                        "do",
                        "did"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We ..................... not like children who ……………. not respect their elders.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do, do",
                        "does, does",
                        "did, does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}